Finding Aid for the Alec Hyatt King Papers, 1859-1998
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Correspondence, 1951-1985, II; Folder 247-279
  - Hill, Richard S. (Richard Synyer), 1901-1961 1951?, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Hinrischen, Max 1962, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Hopkinson, Cecil November 25, 1970, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Hose, H. F. February 5, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Kerslake, John F. March 23, 1956, 2 leaves (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - King, A. Hyatt (Alec Hyatt), 1911-1994 1952-1982, 7 leaves (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - London Choral Society. February 1966, 8 leaves; Regarding John Tobin edition of Handel's Messiah (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Minchin, Leslie T. June 29, 1982, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Muirs, Percival June 1, 1964, 1 leaf; On behalf of Elkin Mathews Ltd. (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Murray, Gregory, 1905- June 3, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Oxford University Press. November 25, 1980, 1 leaf; Signed "Robin"; with 11 folded leaves, photocopies of illustrations from a vocal score of Weber's Der Freischutz (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Pequeno, Mercedes Reis 1968, 1 leaf; Received with Exposicao comemorativa do centenario do nascimento de Francisco Braga (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Postolka, Milan, 1932- December 23, 1980, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Rackwitz, Werner September 29, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Rehm, Wolfgang August 26, 1980, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Rosenthal, Albi, 1914- February 8, 1985, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Vetterlein, Hans August 2, 1972, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Wheeler-Bennett, Richard C. December 3, 1985, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - White, Eric Walter, 1905-1985 February 19, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Unidentified December 18, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 7, Folder 279)
- Complete journal issues, 1956-1998, III; Folder 280-289
  Complete journal issues without designation of specific author as sender.
  Arranged alphabetically by journal title and then chronologically.
  - Cambridge Opera Journal, July 1989 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Cambridge Opera Journal, July 1992 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Chronique Philidorienne, 1980, 3 issues (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Info RISM, August 1991 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Israel Studies in Musicology, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Leading Notes, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Leading Notes, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Library Trends, April 1960, Special issue, edited by Vincent Duckles: Music Libraries and librarianship (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Musical Times, April 1959, Handel Bicentenary Number (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Studien zur Musikwissenschaft, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 289)
- Institutional documents, 1930-1985, IV; Folder 290-306
  Publications include membership lists, congress reports, and organization descriptions.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of the institution.
  - Bibliographical Society (Great Britain), 1960, 1 item; List of members (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Dansk musikbiblioteksforening, 1973, 1 item; List of members and organization history (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Ermuli Trust (Great Britain), 1985, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - International Association of Music Libraries, 1958-1985, 6 items; 4 lists of members, 1 annual report (1980), and 1 conference booklet (1985) (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - International Association of Music Libraries. Ländergruppe der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik, 1959, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - International Federation of Library Associations, 1955, 1 item; List of participants, 1955 Congress, Brussels (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - International Mendelssohn-Schumann Conference, 1982, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - International Music Council, 1985, 1 item; Conference booklet (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - International Musicological Society, 1930, 1961, 1965, 1972, 4 items; 1 list of members (1965) and 3 congress booklets (1930, 1961, 1972); the 1930 booklet is also for the International Society for Contemporary Music festival (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Musicians Benevolent Fund (London, England), circa 1960, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - National Library of Scotland, 1956, 1 item; Booklet: The opening of the new library by Her Majesty the Queen, the fourth of july nineteen hundred and fifty-six (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - National Music Committee of Great Britain, 1953, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - National Music Council of Great Britain, 1960, 1 item; Conference booklet (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Österreichische Akademie der Wissenschaften, 1970, 1 item; Booklet for Beethoven Symposion, Vienna, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Royal Musical Association, 1971, 1 item; Conference booklet (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - University of California, Los Angeles. Institute of Ethnomusicology, 1961, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill. Dept. of Music, 1964, 1 item; Descriptive booklet (Box 9, Folder 306)
- Exhibition catalogs, 1951-1985, V; Folder 307-325
  Catalogs of exhibitions about composers, musical instrument collections, holdings, and other themes.
  Arranged alphabetically by country, then city, then institution name, and finally by title of the exhibition.
  - Brazil. Rio de Janiero. Biblioteca Nacional (Brazil). Exposição comemorativa do centenario do nascimento de Francisco Braga (1868-1945), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Brazil. Rio de Janiero. Biblioteca Nacional (Brazil). Exposição comemorativa do sesquicentenário do nascimento de Fryderyk Chopin, 1810-1849, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Brazil. Rio de Janiero. Biblioteca Nacional (Brazil). Seção de Música e Arquivo Sonoro. Beethoven no Rio de Janiero 1833-1889, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - England. Camden (London, England). St. Pancras Library. Delius and America, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - England. Hull (England). University of Hull. Early instruments & their music, an exhibition: descriptive catalogue, 1978, Catalog by Graham Saunders (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - England. London. Christie's. Creative spirit in the nineteenth century: an exhibition of manuscripts from the British Library's Stefan Zweig Collection, undated (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - England. London. Galpin Society. British musical instruments, 1951, Accompanied by typescript summary of exhibit (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - England. London. Harrods Ltd. Handel exhibition at Harrods: list of exhibits, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - England. London. Lambeth Palace Library. Catalogue of an exhibition of recent gifts and accessions, 1950-1960 to mark the 350th anniversary of the foundation of Lambeth Palace Library 1610, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - England. London. National Portrait Gallery (Great Britain). George Frideric Handel (1685-1759): a checklist of exhibits, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - England. London. Royal Festival Hall. Gustav Holst: centenary exhibition, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - England. London. Upper Grosvenor Galleries. Music in painting: Christmas exhibition, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - France. Besançon. Besançon (France). Musée des beaux-arts. Georges Minot, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Germany. Berlin. Geheimes Staatsarchiv Preussischer Kulturbesitz. Musikautographe aus dem Besitz der Staatsbibliothek Preuss. Kulturbesitz, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Italy. Milan. Biblioteca Nazionale Braidense. Musica nelle biboteche milanesi, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Poland. Katowice. Akademia Muzyczna im. Karola Szymanowskiego w Katowicach. Biblioteka Glówna. Exlibris muzyczny w zbiorach Biblioteki Panstwowej Wyzszej Szkoly Muzycznej w Katowicach = Musical ex libris book plates in the collection of the State Music College Library in Katowice, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Scotland. Edinburgh. National Library of Scotland. Cecil Hopkinson collection of Hector Berlioz: a special exhibition, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Spain. Pontevedra. Biblioteca publica de Pontevedra. Catalogo de Exposicion Bela Bartok, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - United States. Washington, D.C.. Smithsonian Institution. Musical instrument collection of the Smithsonian Institution, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 325)
- Vendor catalogs, circa 1920-1975, VI; Folder 326-342
  Vendors include music publishers, antiquarian book dealers, and one instrument maker.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of the vendor.
  - Artia. Antonin Dvorak, 1841-1904: complete edition, 1955, Sales brochure for new edition of Dvorak's works (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - B. Schott's Söhne. Arnold Schönberg: Samtliche Werke, undated, Prospectus for critical edition (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Aaron Copland, 1973, Catalog of works and discography (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Benjamin Britten 1971, Catalog of works (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Gottfried von Einem, 1972, Catalog of works and discography (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Operas and ballets: illustrated catalogue, 7th ed. 1966 (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Serge Prokofieff, 1975, Catalog of works (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Sergei Rachmaninoff, 1973, Catalog of works (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Boosey & Hawkes. Sound of wood: the story of the B & H clarinets, 1960, Unattributed article in Boosey & Hawkes' Music & Educational Gazzette (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Christie's. Autograph letters of George Friedrich Handel and Charles Jennens, 1973, Illustrated catalogue (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - First Edition Bookshop, Ltd.. Catalogue of catalogues: thematic, auction sales, publishers', composers' libraries, bibliographies and other reference works, 1968, Catalogue no. 82 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Leo Liepmannssohn Antiquariat (Berlin, Germany). Katalog 215: Autographen, 192-, Music issue (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - National Library for the Blind (Great Britain). Catalogue of organ music, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - Otto Haas (A. & M. Rosenthal). Hommage de l'auteur: a selection of musical dedication copies exhibited at the International Antiquarian Book Fair, Zurich, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Robert Morley and Co.. Morley pianoforte and harpsichord galleries, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Theodore Front Musical Literature. Catalogue 17: New books on music, H-N, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - University of London. Library. Union list of periodicals on music in the libraries of the University of London and some other London libraries, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 342)
- Programs, 1949-1998, VII; Folder 343-376
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1949, 1 program; Girton College Music Society performance of Cavalieri's La rappresentazione di anima e di corpo (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - 1950, 3 programs; 1 London Choral Society performance of Handel's Messiah and 2 Wiener Staatsoper (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - 1954, 6 programs; Including: Wiener Staatsoper (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - 1955, 6 programs; Including: Münchner Kammerspiele, Silbernen Kapelle zu Innsbruck, Wiener Staatsoper, Städtische Bühnen (Frankfurt), Bayerische Staatstheater (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - 1956, 2 programs; Including: Wiener Staatsoper (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - 1958, 3 programs; Including: Bühnen der Stadt Köln, May T. Morrison Festival of Music (Berkeley, California), Staatliche Hochschule für Musik Köln (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - 1959, 1 program; Handel bicentenary concert, North London Collegiate School (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - 1960, 1 program; Schubert Festival, University of Nottingham (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - 1961, 1 program; Narodni divadlo v Praze (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - 1962, 1 program; Kaiser Wilhelm-Gedächtniskirche (Berlin, Germany) Bach-Chor; Royal Philharmonic Society (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - 1963, 2 programs; Including: Narodni divadlo v Praze performance of Martinu's Julietta and Smetana's Prodana nevesta (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - 1964, 1 program; University of Maryland Singers (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - 1965, 9 programs (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - 1966, 2 programs; Including: Sadler's Wells Opera (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - 1967, 3 programs; Including: Sadler's Wells Opera, Slovene Philharmonia, Royal Opera House (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - 1968, 2 programs; Including: Archie Camden, Final performance of Sadler's Wells Opera at Sadler's Wells Theatre (Box 10, Folder 358)
  - 1970, 3 programs; Glyndebourne, Royal Philharmonic Society, Berliner Zentralbibliothek (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - 1971, 4 programs; Aldeburgh Festival, Halle Handel Festival, Royal Opera House, St. John's, Smith Square (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - 1972, 4 programs; Glyndebourne, Halle Handel Festival, Tribute to Ralph Vaughan Williams, Sadler's Wells Opera (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - 1973, 1 program; Handel Festival of the German Democratic Republic (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - 1974, 3 programs; Including: Handel Festival of the German Democratic Republic, Music at the Maltings (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - 1975, 5 programs; Handel Festival of the German Democratic Republic, New Zealand Dorian Choir, Kenwood Lakeside, Westminster Abbey service for Sir Arthur Bliss, Aldeburgh Festival (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - 1976, 1 program; Aldeburgh Festival (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - 1977, 2 programs; Including: Snape Maltings (Box 11, Folder 366)
  - 1978, 4 programs; Handel Festival of the German Democratic Republic, Royal Philharmonic Society (Beethoven Bust), Phoenix Opera, Royal Opera House (Box 11, Folder 367)
  - 1979, 2 programs; Handel Festival of the German Democratic Republic, London Symphony welcomes Claudio Abbado as its principal conductor (Box 11, Folder 368)
  - 1980-1981, 2 programs; Festival Musica Theatralis (Brno), Camden Festival (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - 1982, 3 programs; Including: Welsh National Opera, London Philharmonic Orchestra golden jubilee concert (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - 1983, 2 progams; Leeds Music Festival (Painting and music), Royal College of Music Charter centenary Concert (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - 1984, 1 program; English National Opera (Britten's Gloriana) (Box 11, Folder 372)
  - 1987, 2 programs; St. John's (Programme of music by Phyllis Tate), Christie's (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - 1991, 1 program; 40 Jahre Johann-Sebastian-Bach-Institut Gottingen (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - 1995, 1 program; Royal National Theatre (Box 11, Folder 375)
  - 1998, 1 program; 47. Deutsches Mozartfest (Box 11, Folder 376)
- Papers related to King's Some British Collectors of Music 1963-1966, VIII; Folder 377-378
  Reviews of the book and photostatic copies of illustrations used in the book.
  - Reviews and correspondence regarding Some British Collectors of Music, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 377)
  - Photostatic copies of documents and illustrations used in Some British Collectors of Music, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 378)
- Monographic titles collected by King, 1859-1998, IX; Folder 379-450
  - Aird & Coghill, Ltd. Specimens of music engraving and printing. Glasgow: Aird & Coghill, Ltd., 1932, 26 pages (Box 12, Folder 379)
  - Beethoven-Zentenarfeier (1927: Vienna, Austria) Beethoven-Zentenarfeier, Wien, 26. bis 31. märz 1927, veranstaltet von bund und stadt. Festbericht vorgelegt vom Exekutivkomitee der feier.. Vienna: Otto Maass' Sohne, 1927, 83 pages (Box 12, Folder 380)
  - Biblioteca Nacional (Brazil) Três séculos de iconografia da música no Brasil. Rio de Janiero: Biblioteca Nacional, Divisão de Publicações e Divulgação, 1974, 1 booklet (18 pages) and 18 illustrations (Box 12, Folder 381)
  - Börsenverein der Deutschen Buchhändler zu Leipzig (Germany) Music from Germany: an exhibition of books, sheet music, scores and records from the German Democratic Republic Leipzig: Druckerei Schkeuditz, 1961, 64 pages, 20 pages of plates (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - Breitkopf & Härtel. Ludwig van Beethoven 1770-1827 Wiesbaden: Breitkopf & Härtel, 1970, 23 pages (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - British Museum. Catalogue of the musical manuscripts deposited on loan in the British Museum by the Royal Philharmonic Society of London. London: British Museum, 1914, 16 pages (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - British Standards Institution. Specification for the presentation of bibliographical information in printed music. London: British Standards Institution, 1971, 12 pages (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - Broder, Nathan. Music in New York City. New York: G. Schirmer, 1961, 12 pages; Title on cover: The Musical Quarterly welcomes the International Musicological Society, American Musicological Society, New York, September 5-11, 1961. (Box 12, Folder 386)
  - Chapuis, Alfred, 1880-1958. Automates des Jaquet-Droz. Neuchâtel: Musée d'histoire, 1951, 30 pages (Box 12, Folder 387)
  - Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872. Handel studies, no. 11: The Dettingen Te Deum and Israel in Egypt. London: Augener, 1859, 32 pages (Box 12, Folder 388)
  - Coke, David. Muse's bower: Vauxhall Gardens, 1728-1786. Sudbury: Gainsborough's House, 1978, 38 pages (Box 12, Folder 389)
  - Colt, C. F., 1911- Colt clavier collection: silver jubilee, 1944-1969. Portsmouth: Grosvenor Press, 1969, 26 pages (Box 12, Folder 390)
  - Coover, James, 1925-2004. Rainbeau catalog: a facsimile edition. unknown: Distant Press, 1962, 10 pages (Box 12, Folder 391)
  - Delius Trust. Delius 1862-1934. London: Delius Trust, 1998, 4 booklets and 3 leaves (Box 12, Folder 392)
  - Deutsch, Otto Erich, 1883-1967. Otto Erich Deutsch zum 80. Geburtstag. Vienna: Österreichische Musikzeitschrift 1963, pages 405-452; Special issue of Österreichische Musikzeitschrift (September 1963). Contains articles by Deutsch, originally published between 1931 and 1961. (Box 12, Folder 393)
  - Deutsche Bücherei (Germany) Regeln zur Katalogisierung der in der Deutschen Bücherei eingehenden Musikalien. Leipzig: Deutsche Bücherei, 1959, 35 leaves (Box 12, Folder 394)
  - Deutsche Staatsbibliothek. Musikabteilung. Musikabteilung der Deutschen Staatsbibliothek Berlin. Berlin: Deutsche Staatsbibliothek. Musikabteilung 1963, 7 pages (Box 12, Folder 395)
  - Deutsche Staatsbibliothek. Musikabteilung. Die Musikabteilung der öffentlichen Wissenschaftlichen Bibliothek, Berlin: Geschichte und Gegenwartsaufgaben, deutsche Musik-Sammlung, Bücher Sondersammlungen, Lesesaal, Kataloge Berlin: Deutsche Staatsbibliothek. Musikabteilung 1953, 7 pages (Box 12, Folder 396)
  - Duft, Johannes, 1915- Gesangskunst - Buchkunst: Handschriften aus dem 8. bis 18. Jahrhundert in der Stiftsbibliothek St. Gallen St. Gallen: Stiftsbibliothek St. Gallen, 1971, 19 pages (Box 12, Folder 397)
  - Elkin, Robert. Short account of the Royal Philharmonic Society. London: Novello, 1948, 15 pages (Box 12, Folder 398)
  - Emerson, June, 1937- Wind music of Gordon Jacob York: June Emerson, 1976, 8 pages; Includes autobiographical notes by Gordon Jacob. (Box 12, Folder 399)
  - Ernest Brown & Phillips. Catalogue of the exhibition of paintings, drawings and lithographs entitled "The Victorian scene". London: Ernest Brown & Phillips, 1956, 27 pages; Foreword by Graham Reynolds. (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Freystätter, Wilhelm, 1835-1892. Musikalischen Zeitschriften seit ihrer Entstehung bis zur Gegenwart. Amsterdam: Frits Knuf, 1971, 139 pages (Box 12, Folder 401)
  - Geneva (Switzerland). Musée d'art et d'histoire. Exposition "Montres et bijoux": avec une présentation d'automates. Geneva: Musée d'art et d'histoire, 1952, 115 pages; Includes Les Automates: Liste des pieces exposees (8 pages). (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - Gerle, Hans, 1500 (ca.)-1570. Specimen de transcription automatique: Tabulatur auff die Laudten: Nuremberg, 1533. Paris: Centre de recherches pluridisciplinaires 1974, 25 pages (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Goodwin, Noël. Story of the Royal Opera House, Covent Garden. London: Midland Bank, 1973, 11 pages (Box 13, Folder 404)
  - Gyimes, Ferenc. Ludwig van Beethoven a magyar könyvtárakban és gyujteményekben; bibliográfia. Budapest: Állami Gorkij Könyvtár, 1970, 107 pages (Box 13, Folder 405)
  - Haags Gemeentemuseum. Muziekbibliotheek. Muziektheorie in de achttiende eeuw: grepen uit de muziekbibliotheek. Hague: Haags Gemeentemuseum, 1966, 16 pages (Box 13, Folder 406)
  - Horniman Museum. List of the instruments included in the Adam Carse collection of musical wind instruments. London: County Council, 1947, 16 pages (Box 13, Folder 407)
  - Illing, Robert, 1917- Est, Barley, Ravenscroft and the English metrical psalter. Adelaide: Libraries Board of South Australia 1969, 37 pages (Box 13, Folder 408)
  - Inter Nationes. There's music in Germany. Bonn: Inter Nationes, 1964, 1968, 2 volumes (Box 13, Folder 409)
  - International Association of Music Libraries. Ländergruppe der Deutschen Demokratischen Republic. Kommission für Musikalienkatalogisierung. Ordnung der Titel im Autorenkatalog der Musikalien: Empfehlungen. Leipzig: IVMB, 1969, 15 pages (Box 13, Folder 410)
  - Jenkins, Ian (Ian Dennis) Greek music: illustrated notes for teachers. London: British Museum Education Service 1983, 13 pages (Box 13, Folder 411)
  - Johann-Sebastian-Bach-Institut Göttingen. Richtlinien für die Mitarbeiter der neuen Bach-Ausgabe. Munich: Mikrokopie, 1950, 28 pages (Box 13, Folder 412)
  - Johann-Sebastian-Bach-Institut Göttingen. Richtlinien für die Mitarbeiter der neuen Bach-Ausgabe. Munich: Mikrokopie, 1966, 29 pages (Box 13, Folder 413)
  - Legh, Charles. Organ at Adlington Hall. London?: Chiswick Press, 1978?, 8 pages and 4 plates (Box 13, Folder 414)
  - Leipzig (Germany). Musikbibliothek. Quellenkwerke zur Händelforschung Katalog. Leipzig: Leipzig (Germany). Musikbibliothek 1959, 29 pages (Box 13, Folder 415)
  - Library of Congress. Music Division. Folk music of the United States and Latin America: combined catalog of phonograph records. Washington, D.C.: Library of Congress, 1948, 52 pages (Box 13, Folder 416)
  - London Symphony Orchestra. Claudio Abbado & the London Symphony Orchestra. London: London Symphony Orchestra, 1979, 13 pages (Box 13, Folder 417)
  - McPeek, Gwynn S. Guide to the carvings of medieval minstrels in Beverley Minster. Beverley: unknown, 198-, 12 pages; Includes 4 page insert about Beverley Minster. Co-authored by Mary McPeek. (Box 13, Folder 418)
  - Mona, Ilona. Hungarian music publication 1774-1867: first summary. Budapest: Hungarian National Committee of the International Association of Music Libraries, 1973, 37 pages (Box 13, Folder 419)
  - Musical Museum (Great Britain) Introduction to the collection at the National Musical Museum. Brentford: British Piano Museum, 1973, 20 pages (Box 13, Folder 420)
  - Musikwissenschaftliches Institut der Universität Wien. Robert Lach: Persönlichkeit u. Werk; Zum 80. Geburtstag. Vienna: Musikwissenschaftliches Institut der Universität Wien, 1954, 31 pages (Box 13, Folder 421)
  - Musioł, Karol. Polska wydawnictwa z zakresu wychowania muzycznego = Polish publications on music education 1945-1973 Bibliography. Katowice: Panstwowa Wyzsza Szkola Muzyczna 1974, 36 pages (Box 13, Folder 422)
  - Musioł, Karol. Research and journalism published by Karol Musioł. unknown: unknown, 1978, 9 pages (Box 13, Folder 423)
  - Newcastle upon Tyne (England). Central Public Library. Music section. Handlist of songs. Newcastle upon Tyne: Newcastle Upon Tyne Public Libraries 1955, 49 pages (Box 13, Folder 424)
  - Newcastle upon Tyne (England). Central Public Library. Music section. Supplementary handlist no. 1 Newcastle upon Tyne: Newcastle Upon Tyne Public Libraries 1955, 27 pages (Box 13, Folder 425)
  - NHK Kokyo Gakudan. NHK Symphony Orchestra, 1964 Tokyo: NHK Symphony Orchestra, 1964, 50 pages (Box 13, Folder 426)
  - Offenbach 1980 Committee. Offenbach, 1819-1880: a tribute London: Offenbach 1980 Committee, 1980, 48 pages (Box 13, Folder 427)
  - Österreichische Nationalbibliothek. Musiksammlung. Eröffnung des Hoboken-Saales in der Musiksammlung der österreichischen Nationalbibliothek: mit einer Dokumentation, Die Musiksammlung 1970-1975. Vienna: österreichische Nationalbibliothek 1976, 49 pages (Box 13, Folder 428)